// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let que5 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Who invented Java Programming?",
      answer: "James Gosling",
      options: [
        "Guido van Rossum",
        "James Gosling",
        "Bjarne Stroustrup",
        "Dennis Ritchie"
        
      ]
    },
      
   
      {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Which one of the following is not a Java feature?",
      answer: "Use of pointers",
      options: [
        "Object-oriented",
        "Use of pointers",
        "Portable",
        "Dynamic and Extensible"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Which of the following is not an OOPS concept in Java?",
      answer: "Compilation",
      options: [
        "Polymorphism",
        "Inheritance",
        "Compilation",
        "Encapsulation"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which exception is thrown when java is out of memory?",
      answer: "OutOfMemoryError",
      options: [
        "MemoryError",
        "OutOfMemoryError",
        "MemoryOutOfBoundsException",
        "MemoryFullException"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which of these packages contains the exception Stack Overflow in Java?",
      answer: "java.lang",
      options: [
        "java.io",
        "java.system",
        " java.lang",
        "java.util"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of these keywords are used for the block to be examined for exceptions?",
      answer: "try",
      options: [
        "check",
        "throw",
        "catch",
        "try"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which one of the following is not an access modifier?",
      answer: "Void",
      options: [
        "Protected",
        "Void",
        "Public",
        "Private"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: " Which of the following is a reserved keyword in Java?",
      answer: "strictfp",
      options: [
        "object",
        "strictfp",
        "main",
        "system"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "In java, jar stands for_____.",
      answer: " None of the above",
      options: [
        "Java Archive Runner",
        "Java Application Resource",
        "Java Application Runner",
        "None of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "How many threads can be executed at a time? ",
      answer: "Multiple threads",
      options: [
        "Only one thread",
        "Multiple threads",
        "Only main (main() method) thread",
        "Two threads"
      ]
    }
      
  ];